B2.
Daniel has found another talk by an environmental expert about how to protect wetlands, listen with him and complete the notes below.
Wetlands are really important for wildlife.
We should try our best to protect wetlands.
There are two main problems for wetlands today.
First, people use the land for farms and buildings.
Another problem is caused by tourists.
As people move through wetlands, they may bring trouble to the animals there or harm the plants.
To help solve these problems, governments can take action by making laws to stop people from building on wetlands.
Governments can also make laws to reduce the number of tourists visiting wetlands and make sure visitors do no harm while they are there.
Local communities should also work together to help protect wetlands.
To keep the ecosystem healthy, they can help clean up pollution and guide tourists.
They can also plant trees to attract more birds, animals and insects.